fantasyfootballxtreme.com 2016-03-12

# Privacy Policy - Visiomente Corporation

Visiomente and its affiliated companies in the U.S.* (collectively, “Visiomente”) believes that the establishment of trust and privacy is instrumental to the continued growth of the Internet. Visiomente also believes that the efficient collection, use and transfer of information serves to enhance the development of the Internet and electronic commerce, provided that such information is handled in a fair and responsible manner. Therefore, in order to inform you of Visiomente’s policies and activities with respect to the collection, use and transfer of information (including personal information) on the Internet, Visiomente provides this Internet Privacy Policy for review by users of its web site.

## Collection of Personal Information

Visiomente collects personal information from users of its web site. Visiomente may collect basic contact information such as name, address, e-mail address, demographic data, and telephone and fax numbers. Visiomente may collect such personal information as part of the registration process for certain areas of its web site. Visiomente may also collect personal information when users submit comments or other messages to Visiomente through its web site. Additionally, Visiomente uses its web site as a recruiting tool, and users of the Visiomente web site may therefore send résumés containing personal information to Visiomente via its or a third party’s web site.

Additionally, Visiomente may collect personal information through its web site by using cookies and clicktrails. All information collected by means of cookies or clicktrails will be anonymized, aggregated and only used by Visiomente to develop and track traffic patterns and the volume of use of its web site. If you do not want to receive a cookie from its web site, you may set your browser to refuse cookies or to notify you when you receive a cookie, which you may then refuse upon such notice.

## Use and Disclosure of Personal Information

Visiomente may use personal information submitted by its users for specific purposes, including:

  * compiling aggregate statistics of the use of its web site;
  * maintenance and administration of the Visiomente web site;
  * following up on comments and other messages that users submit to Visiomente through its web site;
  * direct marketing and promotional efforts by or on behalf of Visiomente (only if the user opts-in to receive such information); and
  * contacting and recruiting individuals who submit résumés through its or a third party’s web site.

Visiomente will not sell or share personal information collected from the Visiomente website with any third-parties.

## Third-Party Suppliers

Like many organizations, we use third-party suppliers to collect, use and otherwise process personal information on our behalf. Our practice is to require such third parties to handle personal information in accordance with Visiomente’s privacy and security policies.

## Legal Disclosures

Visiomente may disclose your personal information in order to enforce our website Terms of Use or in urgent circumstances to protect personal safety, the public or Visiomente’s websites. It is also possible that we may be required by law to disclose your personal information pursuant to judicial or other government subpoenas, warrants, or orders, potentially, in any country where we do business.

## Correcting, Updating and Removing Personal Information

If a user’s personal information changes or is incorrect, please contact Visiomente.com so that Visiomente may make any necessary updates or corrections. Additionally, in the event that a user of the Visiomente web site does provide personal information and later wishes to have Visiomente remove the personal information, please contact support@visiomente.com in order to do so.

## Data Security and Integrity

Visiomente has put in place certain technological and procedural security functions in order to protect the personal information it collects, uses or transfers from loss, misuse, alteration or destruction. In addition, Visiomente will use reasonable efforts to remove a user’s personal information when it is no longer required for the purposes set forth above. However, Visiomente cannot guarantee that such the loss, misuse, alteration, destruction or retention will never occur, and makes no representations to this effect.

## Third Party Websites

The Visiomente web site may provide links to third party web sites. Visiomente does not make any representations or warranties with respect to such third party web sites. Users of the Visiomente web site should be aware the owners and operators of such third party web sites might collect, use or transfer personal information under different terms and conditions than Visiomente. Upon linking to a third party web site, users of the Visiomente should inform themselves of the privacy policies of such third party web sites.

## Consumer Recourse

If you have any questions or concerns regarding the Visiomente Internet Privacy Policy, please contact us at support@visiomente.com.

Visiomente reserves the right to amend this Internet Privacy Policy at its sole discretion at any time.
